adwordaccelerator.com 2005-12-19

# AdWordAccelerator - Privacy Policy

**AdWordAccelerator Privacy Policy**

Next Generation Professionals Company is committed to each customer's privacy and will do everything within its power to protect this right. 

**Personal Data Transmissions Are Encrypted**

When placing an order or logging into one of our systems, all of your personal information is protected via encryption. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry standard, for encrypting all personal information, including name, address and credit card numbers. 

**Next Generation Professionals Company Will Not Sell Your Personal Information**

At Next Generation Professionals Company we make sure that all of your personal information is kept confidential. We have no immediate or future plans to sell this information in any way, since we wish to continue a long-lasting and trusting relationship between our clients and company.

**Cookie Policy Statement**

Our website uses a minimal amount of cookies, mostly for the ordering process and possibly for future surveys. No personal or identifiable information is stored within any cookies at any time.

**Sending Notifications/Newsletters**

Occasionally, we made need to contact clients with issues that require resolution (e.g., billing problems). In such cases we will use your contact information to send the necessary notifications. In addition to this, for those who choose to opt-in to our mailing list, we will send occasional newsletters, promotions, etc., in order to inform our clients of products, discounts, etc. that might be of interest. 

We reserve the right to change or update this privacy policy at any time as we see fit.
